Hong Li

joeleehong@gmail.com | 480-787-9331 | Portfolio

Summary

Recent Digital Culture graduate with a background focuses on web development. Experience in building web applications with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. Excited for a career in front-end development and acquiring more skills along the way.

Work Experience

Frontend Developer Intern, Chainlink Research

07/2022 - 03/2023

- Fixed WordPress site layout using HTML and block editor
- Fixed images and text layouts for over 100 research articles
- Took part in UI design with the lead frontend developer and the founder of Chainlink Research

Course Grader, Herberger Institute for Design and the Arts

01/2022 - 05/2022

Arizona State University

- Graded student assignments done in p5.js
- Graded 30 to 70 assignments each week with a strict deadline
- Read and evaluated code and provided feedback

Project Experience

IMDB Movie Directory, Herberger Institute for Design and the Arts

03/2022 - 05/2022

Arizona State University

- A movie directory site built with React that can search for movies and direct to the corresponding IMDb pages.
- Utilized third party API to get data from IMDB and displayed corresponding movie posters
- Hosted on Github Page: Demo page

E-Commerce Website Mockup

05/2023 - 07/2023

- Designed layout for an ecommerce website mockup
- Implemented a cart feature and multiple categories of potential products, and connected them with interactive features
- Utilized React, Redux toolkit for data/state management, and hosted using Github Page: Demo page

Technical Skills

Languages: JavaScript, C#, HTML/CSS, Java, SQL, Python

Frameworks and Libraries: React, React toolkit, Bootstrap 4, Svelte, D3.js

Education

Master of Science, Digital Culture

Arizona State University

08/2020 - 05/2022

Tempe, AZ

Bachelor of Science, Computer Information Systems

Arizona State University

08/2014 - 08/2018

Tempe, AZ